tapjoy.net 2011-05-11

# Tapjoy Privacy Policy

## We hate spam more than you do!

Thank you for your interest in Tapjoy, Inc. ("Tapjoy") and our web sites located at [www.offerpalmedia.com](http://www.offerpalmedia.com/), [www.gamepoints.com](http://www.gamepoints.com/), [www.tapjoy.com](https://www.tapjoy.com/), and our other services, including the Offerpal Wallet Facebook application (collectively, the "Tapjoy Platform"). Tapjoy values the privacy of the users, subscribers, members, and others who visit and use the Tapjoy Platform (collectively or individually, "you" or "Users").

By using the Tapjoy Platform, you expressly consent to the information handling practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our Privacy Policy, please do not use the Tapjoy Platform.

This Privacy Policy should be read in connection with, and is incorporated by reference into, the terms of use that govern the particular Tapjoy service you are using. Your use of the Tapjoy Platform and any personal information you provide to Tapjoy through the Tapjoy Platform are subject at all time to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.

### 1\. The Information Tapjoy Collects

User-provided Information: You may provide to Tapjoy what is generally called "personally identifiable" information (such as your name, email address, gender, age, postal mailing address, telephone number and billing information) if you upload or download certain content or products to or from the Tapjoy Platform, enter contests or sweepstakes, take advantage of promotions, respond to surveys, register and subscribe for certain services, or otherwise use the features and functionality of the Tapjoy Platform. You may also provide to Tapjoy demographic information and information related to social networking sites you use, such as the name, address and description. By using the Offerpal Wallet Facebook application, Offerpal will have access to your transaction history on the Tapjoy Platform and user activity within some Facebook applications.

"Cookies" Information: When you access the Tapjoy Platform, we may send one or more cookies - small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer. Tapjoy may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Tapjoy Platform. Both session cookies and persistent cookies can be removed. Please review your web browser "Help" file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings. Some of our business partners (e.g. advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Tapjoy only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

"Automatically Collected" Information: When you access the Tapjoy Platform or open one of our HTML emails, we may automatically record certain information from your system by using different types of tracking technology. This "automatically collected" information may include Internet Protocol address ("IP Address"), a unique user ID, version of software installed, system type, screen resolutions, color capabilities, plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords, JavaScript enablement, the content and pages that you access on the Tapjoy Platform, and the dates and times that you visit the Tapjoy Platform, paths taken, and time spent on sites and pages.

### 2\. Web Beacons

Our web pages may contain electronic image requests (called a "single-pixel gif" or "web beacon" request) that allow us to count page views and to access cookies. Any electronic image viewed as part of a web page, including an ad banner, can act as a web beacon. Web beacons are typically 1-by-1 pixel files, but their presence can usually be seen within a browser by clicking on "View" and then on "Source." We may also include web beacons in HTML-formatted newsletters that we send to opt-in subscribers in order to count how many newsletters have been read. Tapjoy web beacons do not collect, gather, monitor or share any personally identifiable information about our web site visitors, they are just the technique we use to compile anonymous information about web site usage.

### 3\. The Way Tapjoy Uses Information

Tapjoy uses the information that you provide or that we collect to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide all of the features and services found on the Tapjoy Platform, to allow us to charge and invoice you, as well as to track user-generated content and Users to the extent necessary to comply as a service provider with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act.

We will use your email address, without further consent, for administrative communications such as notifying you of major Tapjoy Platform updates, for customer service purposes, to address copyright infringement or defamation issues, or to contact you regarding any content that you have posted to or downloaded from the Tapjoy Platform.

Tapjoy uses all of the information that we collect to understand the usage trends and preferences of our Users, to improve the way the Tapjoy Platform works and looks, and to create new features and functionality.

Tapjoy may use "Automatically Collected" information and "Cookies" information to: (a) automatically update the Tapjoy application on your system; (b) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you access the Tapjoy Platform, and otherwise "personalize" your experience; (c) monitor aggregate site usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages accessed; and (d) track your entries, submissions, and status in any promotions or other activities

### 4\. When Tapjoy Discloses Information

Tapjoy does not share your personally identifiable information with unrelated organizations for their marketing or promotional uses without your prior express consent. Please be aware, however, that any personally identifiable information that you voluntarily choose to display on any publicly available portion of the Tapjoy Platform or related sites becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others without restriction.

We may disclose some limited User information to affiliated companies or other businesses or persons to: provide web site hosting, development, maintenance, support, and security services; fulfill orders; validate credit card numbers; conduct data analysis and create reports; offer certain functionality; and assist Tapjoy in improving the Tapjoy Platform and creating new services features. We generally require that these parties process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy, we authorize only a limited use of such information, and we require these parties to use reasonable confidentiality measures. We may also disclose some limited User information to third parties in connection with processing your request to redeem Offerpal virtual currency for virtual currency or virtual goods offered by such third party.

Tapjoy may share aggregate statistical information gathered from you and other Users with advertisers, business partners, sponsor or other third parties. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of visitors visited a certain area on a web site

Tapjoy may disclose User information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright law) or respond to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant in the manner required by the requesting entity.

Tapjoy also reserves the right to disclose User information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability; protect Tapjoy from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; to investigate and defend ourselves against third-party claims or allegations; to assist government enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of the Tapjoy Platform; enforce the Terms of Use; or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Tapjoy, our Users, or others.

### 5\. Your Choices

You may, of course, decline to share your personally-identifiable information with Tapjoy, in which case Tapjoy will not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionality found on the Tapjoy Platform. You may update, correct, or delete your user information and preferences on the account applicable information page, such as "My Account - Account Settings", or "My Account - Account Information".

We recommend you do not divulge your account password to anyone. Tapjoy will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited telephone call or e-mail. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE SECRECY OF YOUR UNIQUE PASSWORD AND ACCOUNT INFORMATION AT ALL TIMES.

### 6\. Our Commitment to Data Security

Tapjoy uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Tapjoy, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Tapjoy makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

If Tapjoy learns of a security systems breach, then we will attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Tapjoy may post a notice on the Tapjoy Platform if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach you should notify us at [help@tapjoy.com](mailto:help@tapjoy.com)

### 7\. Our Commitment to Children's Privacy,

IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, THEN PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE TAPJOY PLATFORM AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER.

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Tapjoy does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under 13 years-of-age. If Tapjoy learns that personally-identifiable information of persons less than 13-years-of-age has been collected on or through the Tapjoy Platform, then Tapjoy will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 who uses the Tapjoy Platform, then please contact Tapjoy at [help@tapjoy.com](mailto:help@tapjoy.com) to have that child's information deleted.

### 8\. International Visitors

For Users visiting the Tapjoy Platform from the European Economic Area or other non-U.S. territories, please note that any data you enter into the Tapjoy Platform will be transferred outside the European Economic Area or such other non-U.S. territory for use by Tapjoy and its affiliates for any of the purposes described herein. In addition, because Tapjoy operates globally, we may make information we gather available to worldwide business units and affiliates. By providing any data on the Tapjoy Platform, you hereby expressly consent to such transfers of your data to the United States or other countries.

### 9\. In the Event of Merger or Sale

In the event that all or a portion of Tapjoy is acquired by, spun out, or merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from Users as part of that merger, spin out, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.

### 10\. Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically, and this will be reflected by a "last modified" date below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. When we modify this Privacy Policy, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you (e.g. by email or by means of a notice on our homepage or a popup upon your subsequent login). Our amended Privacy Policy will automatically take effect 30 days after we provide notice of the change, except that (i) we will not, without your consent, use your previously collected personally identifiable information in a manner inconsistent Privacy Policy in effect when we received that information, and (ii) if you do not agree with any changes to the Privacy Policy, you may terminate your account ceasing use of the Offerpal Service.

### 11\. Date Last Modified

Privacy Policy last modified on November 9th, 2010.

### 12\. Unsolicited E-mails

Tapjoy does not send unsolicited e-mails to non-public addresses or to anyone who has asked us not to contact him or her. Any newsletters that we send are only sent to those who have subscribed to them. To stop receiving e-mails or newsletters from Tapjoy, click on the unsubscribe link in the e-mail or newsletter.

### 13\. Tapjoy Contact Information

Please contact Tapjoy with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, your personal information, and our third-party disclosure practices or your consent choices at: Tapjoy Inc., 111 Sutter Street, 13th Floor, San Francisco, CA 94104, USA or by email at [help@tapjoy.com](mailto:help@tapjoy.com). We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days of its receipt.

### 14\. Opt-Out

To opt your mobile device out of Tapjoy services, please submit your device id below. 

_iOS Devices:_ Connect your device to iTunes and click on the Serial Number to reveal your device id. (Identifier - UDID)

_Android Devices:_ From your device, go to Settings -> About Phone -> Status. Your device id will be listed either as IMEI or MEID depending on your carrier.
